http://www.marksunderland.com/privacy-policy

PortfolioLatest workStockCalendarsCardsJigsawsWorkshopsSubscribeAboutContactBlog|LightboxAccountCart
Privacy policy
Mark Sunderland Photography is a private business based in Knaresborough, North Yorkshire, England.
Your privacy is important to us.  This privacy policy explains what information we collect about you, how we use it, how long we keep it and your rights relating to our use of your data - please take a moment to review this information.
What data we collect from you and why
We collect personal data such as name, postal address, email address and so on for the purpose of fulfilling your specific request made via this website e.g. creating an account, placing an order, making an enquiry or subscribing to a mailing list.
We take all reasonable precautions to keep your data secure.  This website uses the PhotoDeck service - please see the PhotoDeck privacy policy for specific information relating to this service including data security.
We will not share your data with anyone without your permission unless compelled to do so by law or where it is necessary for specific information to be shared in order to fulfil your request - for example, if you order a fine art print from us we'll need to pass on your name and delivery address to our print partner, One Vision Imaging.
Note that we do not store your credit card details - these details are only collected by our payment processor, PayPal.
If you licence one of our images we'll also keep details of the image usage in our local licensing database which may contain basic contact details such as name and email address.
How long we keep your data
We will retain your data on the PhotoDeck platform for as long as we use the PhotoDeck service, so that you can have access to your order history, any lightboxes you have created and so on.
We will retain certain financial information such as invoices as hard copies for as long as required under statutory regulations.
We need to keep details of image usages in our local licensing database indefinitely in order to manage image rights, but any personal data associated with the usage can be removed once the licence period is over if you wish.
Access to your information and correction
You may request access to the data we hold about you.  If you would like a copy of your data then please get in touch using the Contacting us details below.
We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate.  You may ask us to correct information you think is inaccurate or you may ask us to delete your data.
Cookies
This website uses cookies.  Cookies are small text files placed on your computer by this website to provide standard internet log information and to support certain functions of this website such as authenticated login and your shopping cart.
When you first visit this site you'll be asked if you want to accept or decline cookies in the cookie bar at the bottom of the page.  You don't have to accept cookies if you don't want to but some of the functionality of the site will not work unless you do.  If you accept cookies and want to remove them later you can use your browser to delete cookies.  For more information on cookies visit www.aboutcookies.org.
This site does not use Google Analytics or other third party tracking cookies.
Other websites
This website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.
In particular, the blog is on the WordPress platform rather than PhotoDeck and therefore has its own cookie policy.
Changes to our privacy policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and will place any updates on this page. Last updated 15 May 2018.You can see previous versions of our privacy policy here: Privacy Policy 20 March 2018.
Contacting us
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy by using our Contact Form or directly by email to contact@marksunderland.com.
If you have any concerns about our handling of your Personal Data that we are unable to address you have a right to raise them with the Information Commissioners Office.
Our mailing list
We won't add you to our email mailing list unless you explicitly give us your consent to do so.  This can be done by clicking the checkbox offered when you create an account or place an order, or you can sign up using the box below.  You can unsubscribe whenever you like - there is a prominent unsubscribe link at the top of every email newsletter we send you.  If you have an account on this website (e.g. because you've placed an order in the past) you can unsubscribe (and re-subscribe if you wish) by unchecking (or checking) the box in the My Profile section when you log in.
Join our mailing list. You can unsubscribe at any time via unsubscribe links.
Powered by PhotoDeck
This site uses cookies.
See our privacy policy for details.
You don't have to accept cookies, but some of the functionality on the site won't work without them.AcceptDecline
